Finding Aid for the Anaïs Nin Papers, ca. 1910-1977 LSC.2066
UCLA Library Special Collections
Anaïs Nin papers
ca. 1910-1977
UCLA Library Special Collections
Nin, Anaïs
LSC.2066
14 Linear Feet (28 boxes)
The papers of Anaïs Nin document the life of the noted diarist and novelist. Nin began her diary at the age of 11 in 1914 when she moved to the United States with her family. She continued to write in her diary as she grew up, married and settled into the role of a banker's wife. The diaries chronicle her interest in psychoanalysis, her literary aspirations and her relationships with various writers and artists, including Otto Rank, Henry Miller and Antonin Artaud. The diaries held by UCLA conclude in 1965. In 1946 her diaries took on a different form. Instead of the bound journals she traditionally used, the diaries became compilations of loose pages which included her diary entries interspersed with letters, ephemera, and other writings by Nin kept together in portfolios. The papers also include manuscripts of some of Nin's short stories and erotica, some correspondence, a number of taped interviews and speeches and appearances by Nin in underground films and a documentary by Robert Snyder.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Anaïs Nin Trust, purchase, 1977.
Gift of Rupert Pole, 1977, 1984.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942334993606533
Biography
Anaïs Nin was born in Neuilly, France, February 21, 1903, to Joaquin Nin and Rosa Culmell and moved to New York in 1914 after her father abandoned the family. She began her diary at this time and continued the diary throughout her life. She married banker Hugh P. Guiler in Cuba in 1923 and moved to Paris with him in 1931, where she published her first book, D.H. Lawrence: an unprofessional study (1932) and associated with and cultivated writers and artists, including Antonin Artaud, Lawrence Durrell, Henry Miller, Gonzalo Moré. Began psychoanalysis with Dr. Réne Allendy and later with Otto Rank. She published The house of incest (1936) and Winter of artifice (1939) while in Europe. Returned to New York and began to publish her own work under the imprint of the Gemor Press, including Under a glass bell (1944), This hunger (1945) and limited editions of The house of incest and Winter of artifice. Her husband, Hugh Guiler, using the name Ian Hugo, became a filmmaker and engraver, while maintaining his banking career. Nin published several more books of fiction, including Ladders to fire (1946), Children of the albatross (1947), The four-chambered heart (1950), A spy in the house of love (1954), Solar barque (1958), Cities of the interior (1959) and Seduction of the minotaur (1961). In 1947 she met Rupert Pole and accompanied him on a cross-country trip from New York to Los Angeles, with stops in New Orleans and Taos. She spent the next several years living in New York and Los Angeles, continuing to write in her diary and establishing herself in the creative community of Los Angeles. She took up permanent residence in Los Angeles in 1961. The publication of the first volume of her diary in 1966 brought Nin world-wide attention. The diaries were subsequently published in 7 volumes, 1966-1980. Unexpurgated volumes were published following the death of Hugh Guiler in 1985. Nin died in Los Angeles in 1977.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of diaries, correspondence, manuscripts, cassette and reel-to-reel tapes of lectures and speeches, film appearances, printed items and memorabilia related to diarist and writer Anaïs Nin. Many of the diaries include letters, photographs, theatre programs, clippings, ephemera and memorabilia tipped and laid in. Some of the correspondents include Hugh Guiler, Rupert Pole, Lawrence Durrell, Henry Miller, Gore Vidal, James Leo Herlihy, Felix Pollak and Alan Swallow.
Related Material
Henry Miller Papers (Collection 110). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections.
Diaries.; Letters (Correspondence).; Authors -- 20th century -- Correspondence.; Women authors, American -- 20th century -- Archives.; Nin, Anaïs -- Archives; Miller, Henry
- Appearances by Anaïs Nin in Film, 1952-1973; (0.5 linear ft. and 1 oversize box)
  Scope and Contents note
  Appearances by Anaïs Nin in films, including a documentary by Robert Snyder.
  - Apertura, 1970.; Color. 6 minutes. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    With Anaïs Nin and Barbara Ward.
  - Bells of Atlantis, 1952.; Color. 10 minutes. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Jazz of lights, 1964.; Color. 16 minutes. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Melodic inversion, 1958.; Color. 8 minutes. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    With Anaïs Nin, Robert de Vries and James Leo Herlihy.
  - Through the magiscope, 1969.; Color. 10 minutes. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anaïs observed. Los Angeles, c1973.; Print. 16 mm. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    A film portrait of a woman as artist by Robert Snyder.
    General note
    Box 18 is an oversize flat box.
- Correspondence, 1944-1972; .025 linear ft. (3 folders)
  Letters Calvin Hall, John Espey, Georges Cleyet and C.L. Baldwin.
  - Letters to Calvin Hall and John Espey, 1968 and n.d.; Holograph, typescript(signed). 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    AN to CH, April 16 (1 leaf) and May 16 (1 leaf), 1968. AN to JE, n.d. (2 leaves).
  - Letters from Anaïs Nin to Georges Cleyet, 1966-1972, n.d.; Holograph, typescript(signed). 18 items. Most of these are notecards, 5 with n.d. or legible postmark. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Also included is a card announcing a memorial service for Anaïs Nin, 21 February 1977, Los Angeles.
  - Letters to C.L. Baldwin, 1944-1949.; Holograph, typescript, typescript(carbon), print. 29 items. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    The letters document a professional relationship in which Nin borrowed money from Baldwin to finance her publishing ventures, as well as a personal relationship which ended bitterly. This was gradually renewed under cordial terms. Nin wrote the preface for Baldwin's book of poems, Quinquivara (New York: Gemor Press, c1944) which had engravings by Ian Hugo.
    A calendar of letters is available in the department.
- Diaries by Anaïs Nin, 1914-1965; 12.4 Linear Feet
  Anaïs Nin began writing her diary at the age of 11 and continued throughout her life. The publication of her diaries, beginning in 1966, coincided with the feminist movement and made her an international celebrity. After her death, unexpurgated editions of her diaries were published. The diaries evolved through the years, beginning with daily entries and thoughts on various subjects. In later years, her diaries became a collection of letters, essays and ephemera collected in portfolios.
  - Published as The Early Diary Of Anaïs Nin, 1914-1920: Linotte (vol.1). New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich [c1978], 0.5 Linear Feet (7 folders)
    Diaries 1-3, 5-8. No diary 4 exists as Anaïs Nin explains in Linotte.
    - Diary 1, 1914 July 25-1915 May 19.; Holograph. In dark blue/black/grey/silver marbled boards with dark blue half leather binding. 176 leaves. 17.5 × 21 cm. (Box 2, Folder 1)
      With photographs, notes, drawings and ephemera laid in the diary.
    - Diary 2, 1915 May 23-1916 May 25.; Holograph. In dark blue/charcoal, silver/gold marbled boards with dark blue half-leather binding. 190 leaves. 17.5 × 21 cm. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Diary 3, 1916 June 5-1918 January 19.; Holograph. In dark blue/charcoal/silver/gold marbled paper with dark blue half-leather binding. 232 leaves. 18 × 21.5 cm. (Box 2, Folder 3)
      With ephemera and letters laid in the diary. Nin's drawings are on the front and back inside covers.
      Diary 4, January 1918-March 1919, was lost. The diary resumes after Nin's sixteenth Birthday.
      For additional information, see Linotte: The early diary of Anaïs Nin.
    - Diary 5, 1919 March 22-1919 August 11.; Holograph. In dark blue/charcoal/silver/gold marbled boards with dark blue half-leather binding. 134 leaves. 20.5 × 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Diary 6, 1919 August 11-1919 October 8.; Holograph. In a Lord & Taylor pocket diary for 1919, with burgundy leather binding. 185 leaves. 9.5 × 15.4 cm. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Diary 7, 1919 October 8-1920 January 27.; Holograph. In a pocket diary for 1920, with burgundy leather binding. 187 leaves. 11.4 × 17 cm. (Box 2, Folder 6)
      In Memoranda section Nin has listed books she read for October 1919-January 1920.
    - Diary 8, 1920 January 28-1920 July 9.; Holograph. In pocket diary for 1920 with burgundy leather binding. 180 leaves. 10.8 × 16.8 cm. (Box 2, Folder 7)
      In the same section, Nin has listed books she read February-June 1920.
      With ephemera and Nin's notes (1 leaf) laid in the Memoranda and Cash Accounts section.
      Diaries 1-8 published as Linotte.
  - Published as The Early Diary Of Anaïs Nin, 1920-1923 (vol.2). New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich [c1982], .50 linear ft. (11 folders)
    Diaries 9-19.
    - Diary 9. My diary, 1920 July 9-September 30.; Holograph. In black leather date book for 1920. pp.1-366. 11 × 17.5 cm. Spine broken. (Box 9, Folder 1)
      AN has listed books read and her thoughts on some of these on pp.[367]-[368].
    - Diary 10. My diary, 1920 September 30-November 21.; In a black leather date book for 1920. pp.1-366. Faded ink due to water damage[?], pp.315-327. (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Illustrations by AN on pp.116, 184. "List of books I have read," p.[367].
      With newspaper clippings and autumn leaves tipped in.
      "Pages & contents." p.[368].
    - Diary 11. My diary, 1920 November 22-1921 January 26.; Holograph. In a black leather date book for 1920. pp.1-366. 11 × 17.5 cm. (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Illustration by AN on p.340, with some clippings tipped in. AN has listed books read in December on pp.[367-368]. "Chronicles of my garden," p.[369].
    - Diary 12. My diary, 1921 27 January-April 8.; Holograph. In a blue leather date book for 1921. pp.1-365. 11 × 17.5 cm. Spine broken. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      AN has listed books read on pp.[367]-[368].
      Index written on endpaper.
      With some clippings tipped in and illustrations by AN on pp.14, 31, 32, 88, 145.
    - Diary 13. My diary, 1921 April 9-May 20.; Holograph. In a dark blue date book for 1921. pp.1-365. 11 × 17.5 cm. Spine broken. (Box 9, Folder 5)
      AN has listed books read and her thoughts on some on pp.[367]-[368].
      "To Mimi." on datebook title page, unsigned.
    - Diary 14. My diary, 1921 May 24-July 17.; Holograph. In a blue date book for 1921. pp.1-365. 11 × 17.5 cm. (Box 9, Folder 6)
      AN has listed books read on p.[367].
    - Diary 15. My diary, 1921 July 19-October 18.; Holograph. In a burgundy leather date book with gilt edges. Pages unnumbered, [1-363]. 12.5 × 19.5 cm. (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Photograph of Hugh Guiler on front flyleaf [negative available].
      Printed pages for September, June 7, December 13 & November 15/16 have been cut out.
      Inscription on second flyleaf, "To my Lost Princess. Time can never crumble a true Devotion!! E.S." [Eduardo Sanchez].
    - Diary 16. My diary, 1921 October 19-June 16.; Holograph. In a dark blue leather date book for 1922. pp.1-369. 11 × 17.5 cm. Spine broken. (Box 9, Folder 8)
      On p.[368] AN has listed books read. Brief index follows list of books.
      Printed pages for February 4-13 & May 21/22 have been cut out.
    - Diary 17. My diary, 1922 January 4-June 16.; Holograph. In burgundy leather date book for 1922 (Red Star Diary). pp.1-368. 13.5 × 20 cm. pp.329-362 have been cut out. (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Photographs of Hugh Guiler on p.3 & 240, AN on p.365.
      With ephemera tipped in. AN has listed books read in January on p.366.
      With inscription on flyleaf from Eduardo Sanchez who presented AN with this diary.
    - Diary 18. Journal d'une fiancée, 1922 June-1923 February.; Holograph. In a Red Star diary for 1922, bound in red cloth. pp.1-368. 13.5 × 20 cm. Spine broken. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Photograph of Hugh Guiler on front endpaper, photographs of AN on front flyleaf, frontispiece, p.223.
      With newspaper clippings tipped in.
      Between pp.188-189, 4 leaves (8pp.) have been tipped in.
      pp.343-344, "Calendar of frivolity of journal of a society girl."
      Printed pages for April 5/6, August 29/30, September 30/October 1 & November 3/4 have been cut out.
    - Diary 19. Journal and note book. Journal d'un espouse [starts on p.35], 1923 February 10-1924 April 5.; Holograph. In a burgundy leather date book. pp.1-313, following pages unnumbered. 10.5 × 16 cm. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Books AN read during 1923-1924 are listed in Addresses Section, p.[367].
  - Published as The Early Diary of Anaïs Nin, 1923-1927 (vol.3). New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich [c1983], 1924-1926; 0.25 Linear Feet
    Diaries 20-23.
    - Diary 20. Journal and Note Book, 1924 April 9-1925 February 23.; Holograph. Written in date book for 1924. Bound in burgundy leather with marbled boards. Title page has red wax seal with coat of arms. pp.[1-366], days past numbered. 13 × 18.5 cm. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      AN has tipped in newsclippings, a cartoon and letters.
      On pp.82-83, 3pp. of an early attempt to begin a journal.
      Drawing of AN (clipping) pasted on rear free endpaper appeared in Life, 22 May[1924?].
      " Calendar of engagements," notes and "Books I want to read" follow p.366.
    - Diary 21. Journal and Note Book, 1925 February 27-December 9.; Holograph. Bound in black and beige marbled boards with red cloth spine. There are 2 black wax seals on title page. pp.1-267. 14 × 21 cm. (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Paris. AN has listed books read, pp.265-267.
      4pp. between 230 and 231 have been cut out.
      "Journal of facts," pp.261-264.
      Postcards, theatre programs and concert programs for Joaquin Nin tipped in.
    - Diary 22. Journal and Note Book, 1925 December 12-1926 July 19.; Holograph. Bound in burgundy/grey marbled boards with burgundy leather spine. With gold wax seal on title page. pp.1-259, following pages unnumbered. 13.5 × 21.5 cm. (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Paris. AN has listed books read and books she wanted to read on p.[270].
      "Journal of facts," pp.263-268.
      Some theatre and concert programs have been tipped in.
    - Diary 23. Journal and Note Book, 1926 July 18-1927 April 10.; Holograph. Bound in burgundy/grey/tan marbled boards with burgundy leather spine. With gold wax seal on title page. pp.1-279. 13.5 × 21.5 cm. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Paris. AN has listed books read on pp.277-278.
      Calling card for "Mr.[sic] & Mme. Hugh P.Guiler" laid in.
      "Journal of facts," pp.263, 279-276.
      AN has tipped in some theatre programs.
  - Published as The Early Diary of Anaïs Nin, 1927-1931 (vol.4). New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich [1985], .50 linear ft. (8 folders)
    Diaries 24-31.
    - Diary 24. Mon Journal and Notes, 1927 May 7-1927 November 6.; Holograph. Bound in burgundy/grey/tan marbled boards with burgundy leather spine. pp.[1-365]. 13.5 × 21.5 cm. (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Paris. "Journal of facts," pp.335-345.
      AN has listed books read and comments on some on pp.[355]-[360].
      "Index" and "Books wanted" follow this.
      AN has tipped in theatre programs and newspaper clippings.
    - Diary 25. Journal and Note Book, 1927 November 9-1928 April.; Holograph. Bound in marbled boards with burgundy leather trim, "Anaïs N. Guiler" written on cover. pp.1-252. 13.5 × 22 cm. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      With trimmed photograph of AN & Hugh Guiler in dance costume tipped in opposite title page aswell as 3 trimmed photographs of another dancer (Capo Miralles?).
      With concert programs tipped in, followed by "Journal of facts," "Index," "Books," "Plays and movies."
    - Diary 26. Journal and Note Book, 1928 April 28-December 27.; Holograph. In marbled boards with burgundy leather trim. pp.1-269. 13.5 × 22 cm. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      "Books," pp.265-266.
      "Journal of facts," pp.[269]-"6," followed by index.
    - Diary 27. Mon Journal and Note Book. John, 1929 January-June 5.; Holograph. pp.1-275. 13.5 × 22 cm. Spine broken and some pages loose. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      pp.179-248 loose after p.244, jumps to another p.179 before continuing with p.245.
      Little sketches throughout, pp.1, 2, 111, 115, 116, 118, 119.
      "Journal of Facts," pp.265-269, "Index," pp.271-273, "Phrases," pp.274-275.
      Photo of John & Pauline Erskine tipped into title page.
      Unidentified photo of a woman tipped in opposite p.1.
      With programs and clippings tipped in.
    - Diary 28. Mon Journal and Note Book. The House, 1929 June 5-December 31.; Holograph. In black leather binding with gilt decoration and gilt edges. pp.1-411. 12 × 17.5 cm. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      "Paris, London, Paris."
      Ephemera, concert programs and photographs tipped in.
      "Index," p.372-375.
      December 10, 1929, AN contrasts Aldous Huxley with Sinclair Lewis, pp.307-312.
      Photographs of interior of AN's apartment tipped in throughout.
      "Books," pp.381-384.
      "Journal of facts," pp.[385]-392.
      p.385 is misnumbered "285."
    - Diary 29. Mon Journal and Note Book. "Writing" and "Dancing." Eduardo, 1930 January 15-November 18.; Holograph. In black leather binding with gilt decoration and gilt edges. pp.1-408. 12 × 17.5 cm. (Box 15, Folder 5)
      "Books read," pp.378-383.
      "Journal of facts," pp.384-406.
      AN's notes on D.H. Lawrence, p.379-381.
      Pencil sketch of AN floating by "Natasha," p.403.
      With concert programs and clippings tipped in.
      Partial index, pp.372-373.
      Negatives available for title page and p.379.
    - Diary 30. Mon Journal and Note Book, 1930 November 24-1931 May.; Holograph. In black leather binding with gilt decoration and gilt edges. pp.1-404. 12 × 17.5 cm. (Box 15, Folder 6)
      "Books read," pp.387-390, "Journal of facts," pp.391-396, "Index," pp.367-372.
      Photograph of AN's apartment (?) tipped in opposite title page and p.380.
      Concert programs and clippings tipped in.
    - Diary 31. Mon Journal and Note Book. The Woman Who Died. Disintegration, 1931 June 5-October 19.; Holograph. In red leather binding. pp.1-251. 11.5 × 18 cm. Slight tear on spine. (Box 15, Folder 7)
      "Books read" and "Journal of facts" follow numbered pages.
      With photographs, postcards and concert programs tipped in.
  - Published as Henry and June: From The Unexpurgated Diary of Anaïs Nin, 1932-1934. San Diego: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich [1986], 1931-1932; 0.5 Linear Feet
    Diaries 32-36.
    - Diary 32. Mon Journal and Note Book. Book II - June, 1931 October 20-1932 February 1.; Holograph. In a black leather binding. pp.1-252. 11.5 × 19 cm. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      "Books read" follows page 252.
      "Journal of Facts" and "Index" follow numbered pages.
      "Anaïs Nin [Guiler]" on title page, with "Guiler"covered.
      "Journal of facts" and "Index" follow numbered pages.
      With a clipping "La Vie de Boheme" re June Miller written by Wambly Bald tipped in.
      Programs and ephemera tipped in.
    - Diary 33. Mon Journal and Note Book. The Possessed, 1932 February 2-[April 15].; Holograph. June and Henry, Eduardo. In burgundy leather binding with gilt decoration. Wax seal on cover. pp.1-309. 11.5 × 17.5 cm. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      "Melanges,," p.23," "Mother's prejudice," p.37, "What Hugh has done for me," pp.38-39.
      "Books read," p.302, horoscope in French, pp.303-308.
      There is a second diary 33, lacking a cover, beginning February 16, "Today I gave up the other journal...," pages unnumbered.
      Journal, "The Possessed" with photo of Henry Miller tipped into front flyleaf.
    - Diary 34. Journal. Note Book. Henry. Rene Allendy, 1932 April 18-June 9.; Holograph. In purple leather binding with gilt decoration. pp.1-317 with index before p.1 and following p.318. 11.5 × 18 cm. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Diary 35. Mon Journal and Note Book. Henry. The Apotheosis and Downfall, 1932 June 9-August.; Holograph. In black leather binding. pp.1-254, followed by list of books read. 11.5 × 18 cm. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Photo of Henry Miller tipped in opposite title page.
      Letter from HM tipped in, p.251.
    - Diary 36. Journal and Note Book. Journal of a Possessed. Henry. Allendy. Ana Maria. June, 1932 August 24-October 23.; Holograph. In black leather binding. pp.1-269 [no p.265], pages misnumbered after 264. 11.5 × 18 cm. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Index opposite title page.
  - Published as Incest. From a Journal of Love. The Unexpurgated Diary of Anaïs Nin, 1932-1934. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich [c1992], .50 linear ft. (10 folders)
    Diaries 37-46.
    - Diary 37. Journal and Note Book. La Folle Lucide. Equilibre, 1932 October 23-December.; Holograph. In black leather binding with wax seal on cover. pp.1-370, followed by continuation of index. 11.5 × 18 cm. (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Index opposite title page. Photo of Henry Miller opposite page 1. Letter from "Fred" laid in between pp.224-225.
    - Diary 38. Uranus. Journal and Note Book. Henry. Allendy. Louise. Andre, 1932 November 24-1933 January 29.; Holograph. In dark blue leather binding with gilt decoration. pp.1-300, followed by index. 13 × 20.5 cm. (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Horoscope for HM tipped in, pp.298-300.
      Photo of Henry Miller tipped in opposite title page and opposite p.1.
      HM has written in the diary, pp.186-205 on 1 January 1933.
      Fragment of letter from HM, p.231.
    - Diary 39. Journal and Note Book. Schizoïde and Paranoia. The Triumph of Magic. Black and white Magic, 1933 January 31-March 12.; Holograph. In black leather binding. pp.1-270, index pages 261-266. 11.5 × 18 cm. (Box 16, Folder 8)
      "Henry, Eduardo, Allendy, Gustavo Duran, Comtesse de Voguï(?), Antonin Artaud."
      "Listed 'amoureaux," p.254, "Three painters, three other Cubans... ," p.255.
      With a pamphlet by Antonin Artaud tipped in, as well as other ephemera and an envelope.
    - Diary 40. Journal and Note Book. Flagellation, 1933 March 12-May.; Holograph. In black leather binding. pp.1-247, index begins [p. 247], rest of pages unnumbered. 11.5 × 18 cm. (Box 16, Folder 9)
      "Books read" follows index.
      With notes in two different hands tipped in after "Books read."
    - Diary 41. Mon Journal and Note Book. Father, 1933 May 7-June.; Holograph. In black leather binding. pp.1-255 with following pages unnumbered, index follows. 11.5 × 18 cm. (Box 16, Folder 10)
      "Henry, Artaud, Steele, Allendy, Nestor."
      AN's note on title page, "And on the seventh day, He rested from His work. Quoted negligently from a book I never read."
      Watercolor by Henry Miller tipped in.
    - Diary 42. Mon Journal and Note Book. Incest, 1933 June 13-August.; Holograph. In purple leather binding with gilt decoration, gilt edges. pp.1-309. 11.5 × 18 cm. Page 73 is in a different hand, signed "R." (Box 16, Folder 11)
      Father, Henry, Antonin Artaud.
      Clipping re Sedlacek laid in, pp.128-129.
    - Diary 43. Mon Journal and Note Book. Father. Henry, 1933 August 12-September 18.; Holograph. In black leather notebook with copper-colored wax seal on cover. pp.1-139. 11.5 × 18 cm. Entries for pp.29-32 are in print rather than script. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Diary 44. Mon Journal and Note Book. Audace, 1933 September 19-November 8.; Holograph. In black leather binding. pp.1-233. 11.5 × 18 cm. Pages unnumbered after 233. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Fig pudding recipe from AN's mother, p.175.
      Caricature of Hugh, p.199.
      Henry Miller business card tipped in title page.
      Copies of excerpts of letter from AN to HM tipped in, pp.130-135.
      "Journal of facts," p.[251], "Index," p.[259].
      "Talk with Rank," pp.221-230.